<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <!--
 SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2021 Carl Schwan <carlschwan@kde.org>
 SPDX-License-Identifier: FSFAP
-->
  <id>org.kde.optiimage</id>
  <name>OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">المحسّن</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">ऑप्टीइमेज</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="sa">ऑप्टिइमेज</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Optibild</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxOptiImagexx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">OptiImage 图像压缩工具</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">OptiImage</name>
  <provides>
    <binary>optiimage</binary>
  </provides>
  <summary>Image optimizer to reduce the size of images</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">مُحسِّن الصور لتقليل حجم الصور</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Optimitzador d'imatges per a reduir la mida de les imatges</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Optimitzador d'imatges per a reduir-ne la mida</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Image optimiser to reduce the size of images</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Bild-optimumigilo por redukti la grandecon de bildoj</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Optimizador de imágenes para reducir su tamaño</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Irudien neurria murrizteko optimizatzaile bat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Kuvakokoa pienentävä kuvaoptimoija</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Outil d'optimisation d'images pour réduire leurs tailles</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Optimizador de imaxes para reducir o tamaño das imaxes.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">ממטב תמונות שנועד להקטין גודל של תמונות</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hi">छवियों का आकार कम करने के लिए छवि अनुकूलक</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Optimisator de imagine per reducer le grandor de imagines</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Ottimiazzatore d'immagini che ne riduce la dimensione</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">გამოსახულებების ოპტიმიზაცია მათი ზომის შემცირების მმიზნით</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">그림 크기를 줄이는 이미지 최적화 도구</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Attēlu optimizēšanas programma, kas palīdz samazināt attēlu izmēru</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Optimalisatie van afbeeldingen om de grootte van afbeeldingen te verminderen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Optymalizator obrazów do zmniejszania rozmiaru obrazów</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sa">चित्राणां आकारं न्यूनीकर्तुं चित्रानुकूलकः</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Optimizator slik za zmanjšanje velikosti slik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Bildoptimering för att reducera bildstorlek</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Görsel Boyutu Eniyileyicisi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Засіб оптимізації зображень, метою якого є зменшення розмірів файлів</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxImage optimizer to reduce the size of imagesxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">用于压缩图像体积的优化工具</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">降低影像大小用的影像最佳化工具</summary>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LGPL-2.1-only</project_license>
  <developer id="kde.org">
    <name>KDE</name>
  </developer>
  <description>
    <p>Optimize your images with OptiImage, a useful image compressor that supports
    PNG, JPEG, WebP and SVG file types.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">حسّن صورك باستخدام المحسّن، وهو ضاغط صور مفيد يدعم أنواع ملفات PNG وJPEG وWebP وSVG</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Optimitzeu les imatges amb l'OptiImage, un compressor d'imatges útil que admet tipus de fitxers PNG, JPEG, WebP i SVG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Optimitzeu les imatges amb OptiImage, un compressor d'imatges útil que admet tipus de fitxers PNG, JPEG, WebP i SVG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Optimise your images with OptiImage, a useful image compressor that supports PNG, JPEG, WebP and SVG file types.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Optimumigu viajn bildojn per OptiImage, utila bildkunpremilo kiu subtenas PNG, JPEG, WebP kaj SVG-dosiertipojn.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Optimice sus imágenes con OptiImage, un útil compresor de imágenes compatible con los tipos de archivo PNG, JPEG, WebP y SVG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Optimizatu zure irudiak OptiImage erabiliz, PNG, JPEG, WebP eta SVG fitxategi motak onartzen dituen irudi konprimatzaile baliagarri bat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Optimoi kuvasi OptiImagella, näppärällä PNG-, JPEG-, WebP- ja SVG-tiedostomuotoja tukevalla kuvapakkaimella.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Optimisez vos images avec OptiImage, un compresseur d'images utile prenant en charge les types de fichiers PNG, JPEG, WebP et SVG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Optimice imaxes con OptiImage, un útil compresor de imaxes compatíbel cos tipos de ficheiro PNG, JPEG, WebP e SVG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">מיטוב התמונות שלך בעזרת OptiImage, דוחס תמונות שתומך בסוגי הקבצים PNG,‏ JPEG,‏ WebP ו־SVG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">OptiImage के साथ अपनी छवियों को अनुकूलित करें, यह एक उपयोगी छवि संपीड़क है जो PNG, JPEG, WebP और SVG फ़ाइल प्रकारों का समर्थन करता है।</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Optimisa tu images con OptiImage, un compressor utile de imagine que supporta typos de file PNG, JPEG, WebP e SVG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Ottimizza le tue immagini con OptiImage, un utile compressore d'immagini che supporta i file PNG, JPEG, WebP e SVG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">დააოპტიმიზეთ თქვენი გამოსახულებები OptiImage-სთან, საჭირო გამოსახულებების შემკუმშავთან, რომელსაც PNG, JPEG, WebP და SVG ფაილის ტიპების სრული მარდაჭერა გააჩნია.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">OptiImage를 사용하여 이미지를 최적화할 수 있습니다. PNG, JPEG, WebP, SVG 파일 형식을 지원합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Optimizējiet attēlus ar „OptiImage“ — noderīgu attēlu saspiešanas programmu, kas atbalsta PNG, JPEG, „WebP“ un SVG attēlu datnes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Optimaliseer uw afbeeldingen met OptiImage, een nuttige comprimeerder die PNG, JPEG, WebP en SVG typen bestanden ondersteunt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Optymalizuj swoje obrazy w OptiImage, użyteczny narzędziu do pakowania obrazów, który obsługuje pliki: PNG, JPEG, WebP oraz SVG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sa">OptiImage इत्यनेन सह स्वस्य चित्राणि अनुकूलितं कुर्वन्तु, यत् उपयोगी चित्रसंपीडकं PNG, JPEG, WebP तथा SVG सञ्चिकाप्रकारं समर्थयति ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Optimizirajte svoje slike z OptiImage, uporabnim kompresorjem slik, ki podpira vrste datotek PNG, JPEG, WebP in SVG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Optimera dina bilder med Optibild, ett användbart bildkomprimeringsverktyg som stöder filtyperna PNG, JPEG, WebP och SVG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">PNG, JPEG, WebP ve SVG türü görselleri destekleyen bir görsel sıkıştırıcısı olan OptiImage ile görsellerinizi eniyileyin.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Оптимізуйте ваші зображення за допомогою OptiImage, корисної програми для стискання файлів зображень, у якій передбачено підтримку типів файлів PNG, JPEG, WebP і SVG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxOptimize your images with OptiImage, a useful image compressor that supports PNG, JPEG, WebP and SVG file types.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">OptiImage 是一款图像压缩优化工具，可以帮助您压缩图像的体积。支持 PNG、JPEG、WebP 和 SVG 等文件格式。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">用 OptiImage 來最佳化您的影像，它支援 PNG、JPEG、WebP 和 SVG 檔案格式。</p>
    <p>It supports both lossless and lossy compression modes with an option whether
    to keep or not metadata of images. It additionally has a safe mode, where a new
    image is created instead of overwriting the old one.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يدعم كلاً من وضعي الضغط بدون فقدان أو مع فقدان البيانات مع خيار الاحتفاظ ببيانات الصور الوصفية أو عدم الاحتفاظ بها. كما يحتوي على وضع آمن، حيث ينشئ صورة جديدة بدلاً من الكتابة فوق الصورة القديمة.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">És compatible tant amb els modes de compressió amb pèrdua i sense, amb una opció per a mantenir o no les metadades de les imatges. A més, té un mode segur, on es crea una imatge nova en lloc de sobreescriure l'antiga.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">És compatible tant amb els modes de compressió amb pèrdua i sense, amb una opció per a mantindre o no les metadades de les imatges. A més, té un mode segur, on es crea una imatge nova en lloc de sobreescriure l'antiga.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">It supports both lossless and lossy compression modes with an option whether to keep or not metadata of images. It additionally has a safe mode, where a new image is created instead of overwriting the old one.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Ĝi subtenas ambaŭ senperdan kaj perdan kunpremajn reĝimojn kun eblo ĉu konservi aŭ ne metadatumojn de bildoj. Ĝi krome havas sekuran reĝimon, kie nova bildo estas kreita anstataŭ superskribi la malnovan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Permite usar los modos de compresión con y sin pérdida, con la opción de conservar los metadatos de las imágenes. También dispone de un modo seguro que crea imágenes nuevas en lugar de sobrescribir las existentes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Galerarik gabeko eta galeradun konpresio moduak, biak onartzen ditu, irudien meta-datuak mantendu edo ez erabakitzeko aukera batekin. Modu seguru bat ere badu, irudi zaharra gainidatzi ordez berri bat sortzeko.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Se tukee sekä häviötöntä että häviöllistä pakkausta ja mahdollistaa kuvien metatiedon säilyttämisen. Lisäksi siinä on turvatila, jossa luodaan uusi kuva vanhaa korvaamatta.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Il prend en charge les modes de compression sans perte et avec perte, ainsi qu'une option pour définir s'il faut conserver ou non les métadonnées des images. Il propose par ailleurs un mode plus sûr, où une nouvelle image est créée au lieu de remplacer l'ancienne.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Permite compresións con e sen perda, cunha opción para manter ou non os metadatos das imaxes. Tamén ten un modo seguro, no que se crea unha nova imaxe en vez de modificar a vella.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">הוא תומך גם במצבים שמאבדים מידע וגם בכאלה שלא עם אפשרות לשמור את נתוני העל של התמונה. בנוסף יש לו גם מצב בטוח, בו נוצרת תמונה חדשה במקום לדרוס את הישנה.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">यह दोषरहित और दोषरहित संपीड़न दोनों मोड का समर्थन करता है, साथ ही इसमें यह विकल्प भी है कि छवियों का मेटाडेटा रखना है या नहीं। इसके अतिरिक्त इसमें एक सुरक्षित मोड भी है, जहाँ पुरानी छवि को अधिलेखित करने के बजाय एक नई छवि बनाई जाती है।</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Il supporta sia modos de compression sin perdita que con perdita con un option si mantener o non le metadatos de imagines. Additionalmente il ha un modo secur, ubi un nove image es create in loco de super scriber ille vetere.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Supporta sia modalità di compressione con perdita che senza, e ha un'opzione per mantenere oppure no i metadati delle immagini. In aggiunta ha una modalità sicura, che crea un'immagine nuova al posto di sovrascrivere quella vecchia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">აქვს ორივე, კარგვის გარეშეც და კარგვითაც შეკუმშვის რეჟიმები არჩევნის საშუალებით, შევინარჩუნოთ გამოსახულების მეტამონაცემები, თუ არა. დამატებით, მას აქვს უსაფრთხო რეჟიმი, სადაც ძველი გამოსახულების თავზე გადაწერის მაგიერ ახალი გამოსახულება იქმნება.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">무손실과 손실 압축을 둘 다 지원하며 이미지 메타데이터 유지 여부를 선택할 수 있습니다. 기존 이미지를 덮어쓰지 않는 안전 모드를 제공합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Tā atbalsta gan saspiešanu ar zudumiem, gan bez zudumiem ar opciju paturēt vai dzēst attēlu metadatus. Tāpat programmā ir iebūvēts drošais režīms, kas izveido jaunus attēlus un nepārraksta jau esošos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Zowel modi voor compressie met als zonder verlies worden ondersteund met een optie voor het al dan niet behouden van metagegevens van afbeeldingen. Bovendien met een veilige modus, waar een nieuwe afbeelding wordt gemaakt in plaats van de oude te overschrijven.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Obsługuje tryby pakowania zarówno bezstratne jak i stratne z możliwością zachowania lub porzucenia metadanych obrazów. Dodatkowo ma tryb bezpieczny, w którym tworzone są nowe obrazy zamiast zastępować stare.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sa">इदं चित्राणां मेटाडाटा स्थापयितव्यं वा न वा इति विकल्पेन सह हानिरहितं हानिरहितं च संपीडनविधानं समर्थयति । अस्य अतिरिक्तरूपेण सुरक्षितः मोडः अस्ति, यत्र पुरातनस्य उपरि लेखनस्य स्थाने नूतनं चित्रं निर्मीयते ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Podpira oba načina stiskanja tako brez izgub kot z izgubami z možnostjo da obdrži ali ne metapodatke slik. Poleg tega ima varen način, kjer se ustvari nova slika namesto, da se prepiše stara.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Det stöder både förlustfri och förstörande komprimeringsmetoder med ett alternativ om du vill behålla metadata för bilder eller inte. Det har dessutom ett säkert läge, där en ny bild skapas istället för att skriva över den gamla.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Görsellerin üst verisinin tutulup tutulmaması seçeneğiyle hem kayıpsız hem de kayıplı sıkıştırma kiplerini destekler. Ayrıca eskisinin üzerine yazmak yerine yeni bir görselin oluşturulduğu güvenli bir kipi de vardır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Передбачено підтримку режимів стискання без втрат та з втратами із можливістю зберігати або відкидати метадані зображень. Крім того, передбачено безпечний режим, у якому програма створює нове зображення замість перезапису старого.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxIt supports both lossless and lossy compression modes with an option whether to keep or not metadata of images. It additionally has a safe mode, where a new image is created instead of overwriting the old one.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">它同时支持有损和无损压缩模式，并可以选择是否要保留图像的元数据。它还有一个安全模式，将压缩后的图像另存为新文件而不是覆盖原文件。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">支援無損和有損壓縮模式，並且可選擇是否保留影像的中繼資料。它也提供安全模式選項，將壓縮後的影像寫入新檔案而不是覆寫舊檔案。</p>
    <p>It uses the following tools:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يستخدم الأدوات التالية:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Utilitza les eines següents:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Utilitza les eines següents:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">It uses the following tools:</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Ĝi uzas la sekvajn ilojn:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Usa las siguientes herramientas:</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Ondoko tresnak erabiltzen ditu:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Se käyttää seuraavia työkaluja:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Il utilise les outils suivants :</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Usa as seguintes ferramentas:</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">משתמש בכלים הבאים:</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">इसमें निम्नलिखित उपकरणों का उपयोग किया जाता है:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Il usa le sequente instrumentos:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Utilizza i seguenti strumenti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">იყენებს შემდეგ პროგრამებს:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">다음 도구를 사용합니다:</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Programmas izmanto šādus rīkus:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">De volgende hulpmiddelen worden gebruikt:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Używa następujących narzędzi:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sa">अस्मिन् निम्नलिखितसाधनानाम् उपयोगः भवति ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Uporablja naslednja orodja:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Det använder följande verktyg:</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Aşağıdaki araçları kullanır:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Використано такі інструменти:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxIt uses the following tools:xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">它使用以下工具程序：</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">它會利用以下工具：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>oxipng for PNG images</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">oxipng لصور PNG</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">«oxipng» per a imatges PNG</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">«oxipng» per a imatges PNG</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">oxipng for PNG images</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">oxipng por PNG-bildoj</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">oxipng para las imágenes PNG</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">oxipng PNG irudietarako</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">oxipng PNG-kuville</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">oxipng pour les images « PNG »</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">oxipng para imaxes PNG.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">oxipng לתמונות PNG</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">PNG छवियों के लिए ऑक्सीपीएनजी</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">oxipng per imagines  PNG</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">oxipng per le immagini  PNG</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">oxipng-ს PNG გამოსახულებებისთვის</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">PNG 이미지: oxipng</li>
      <li xml:lang="lv">„oxipng“ PNG attēlu apstrādei</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">oxipng voor PNG-afbeeldingen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">oxipng do obrazów PNG</li>
      <li xml:lang="sa">PNG चित्राणां कृते oxipng</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">oxipng za slike PNG</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">oxipng för PNG-bilder</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">PNG görselleri için oxipng</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">oxipng для зображень PNG</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxoxipng for PNG imagesxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">oxipng (PNG 图像压缩)</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">對 PNG 影像使用 oxipng</li>
      <li>jpegoptim for JPEG images</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">jpegoptim لصور JPEG</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">«jpegoptim» per a imatges JPEG</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">«jpegoptim» per a imatges JPEG</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">jpegoptim for JPEG images</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">jpegoptim por JPEG-bildoj</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">jpegoptim para las imágenes JPEG</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">jpegoptim JPEG irudietarako</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">jpegoptim JPEG-kuville</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">jpegoptim pour les images « JPEG »</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">jpegoptim para imaxes JPEG.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">jpegoptim לתמונות JPEG</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">JPEG छवियों के लिए jpegoptim</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">jpegoptim per images JPEG</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">jpegoptim per le immagini JPEG</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">jpegoptim-ს JPEG გამოსახულებებისთვის</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">JPEG 이미지: jpegoptim</li>
      <li xml:lang="lv">„jpegoptim“ JPEG attēlu apstrādei</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">jpegoptim voor JPEG-afbeeldingen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">jpegoptim do obrazów JPEG</li>
      <li xml:lang="sa">JPEG चित्राणां कृते jpegoptim</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">jpegoptim za slike JPEG</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">jpegoptim för JPEG-bilder</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">JPEG görselleri için jpegoptim</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">jpegoptim для зображень JPEG</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxjpegoptim for JPEG imagesxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">jpegoptim (JPEG 图像压缩)</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">對 JPEG 影像使用 jpegoptim</li>
      <li>scour for SVG images</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">scour لصور SVG</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">«scour» per a imatges SVG</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">«scour» per a imatges SVG</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">scour for SVG images</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">scour por SVG-bildoj</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">scour para las imágenes SVG</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">scour SVG irudietarako</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">scour SVG-kuville</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">scour pour les images « SVG »</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">scour para imaxes SVG.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">scour לתמונות SVG</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">एसवीजी छवियों के लिए खोज करें</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">scour per images SVG</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">scour per le immagini SVG</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">scour-ს SVG გამოსახულებებისთვის</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">SVG 이미지: scour</li>
      <li xml:lang="lv">„scour“ SVG attēlu apstrādei</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">scour voor SVG-afbeeldingen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">scour do obrazów SVG</li>
      <li xml:lang="sa">SVG चित्राणां कृते scour</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">scour za slike SVG</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">scour for SVG-bilder</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">SVG görselleri için scour</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">scour для зображень SVG</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxscour for SVG imagesxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">scour (SVG 图像压缩)</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">對 SVG 影像使用 scour</li>
      <li>cwebp for WebP images</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">cwebp لصور WebP</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">«cwebp» per a imatges WebP</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">«cwebp» per a imatges WebP</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">cwebp for WebP images</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">cwebp por WebP-bildoj</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">cwebp para las imágenes WebP</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">cwebp WebP irudietarako</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">cwebp WebP-kuville</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">cwebp pour les images « WebP »</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">cwebp para imaxes WebP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">cwebp לתמונות WebP</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">WebP छवियों के लिए cwebp</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">cwebp per imagines  WebP</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">cwebp per le immagini WebP</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">cwebp-ს WebP გამოსახულებებისთვის</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">WebP 이미지: cwebp</li>
      <li xml:lang="lv">„cwebp“ „WebP„ attēlu apstrādei</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">cwebp voor WebP-afbeeldingen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">cwebp do obrazów WebP</li>
      <li xml:lang="sa">WebP चित्राणां कृते cwebp</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">cwebp za slike WebP</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">cwebp för WebP-bilder</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">WebP görselleri için cwebp</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">cwebp для зображень WebP</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxcwebp for WebP imagesxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">cwebp  (PNG 图像压缩)</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">對 WebP 影像使用 cwebp</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/optiimage/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=OptitImage</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://invent.kde.org/graphics/optiimage</url>
  <categories>
    <category>Graphics</category>
  </categories>
  <custom>
    <value key="KDE::matrix">#plasma-mobile:kde.org</value>
  </custom>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.optiimage.desktop</launchable>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/optiimage/optiimage2.png</image>
      <caption>OptiImage main view showing a list of images getting processed</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista principal de l'OptiImage que mostra una llista d'imatges que s'estan processant</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista principal d'OptiImage que mostra una llista d'imatges que s'estan processant</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista principal de OptiImage con la lista de imágenes que se están procesando</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">OptiImage-ren ikuspegi nagusia, prozesatzen ari diren irudien zerrenda bat erakusten duena</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Vue principale de Optiimage présentant une liste d'images en cour de traitement</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">A vista principal de OptiImage cunha lista de imaxes en procesamento.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">התצוגה הראשית של OptiImage שמציגה רשימה של תמונות שעוברות עיבוד</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hi">ऑप्टीइमेज मुख्य दृश्य संसाधित हो रही छवियों की सूची दिखा रहा है</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Vista principal de OptiImage monstrante un lista de images que il va processar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">La vista principale di OptiImage che mostra un elenco di immagini che vengono elaborate</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">Optiimage-ის მთავარი ხედი, რომელიც აჩვენებს გამოსახულებების სია, რომლებიც მუშავდება</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">OptiImage hoofdweergave die een lijst toont van afbeeldingen om te worden verwerkt</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sa">OptiImage मुख्यदृश्यं यत् संसाधितानां चित्राणां सूचीं दर्शयति</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Glavni pogled OptiImage, ki prikazuje seznam slik, ki se obdelujejo</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">OptiImage ana görünümü, işlenen bir görsel listesini gösteriyor</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Основна панель OptiImage зі списком зображень, які буде оброблено</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxOptiImage main view showing a list of images getting processedxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">OptiImage 主视图显示正在处理的图像列表</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">OptiImage 的主檢視，顯示正在被處理的影像</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release version="1.0.0" date="2024-11-30">
      <url>https://carlschwan.eu/2024/11/24/optiimage-1.0.0-is-out/</url>
      <description>
        <p>Initial release of OptiImage</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
