<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <!--
 SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2021 Carl Schwan <carlschwan@kde.org>
 SPDX-License-Identifier: FSFAP
-->
  <id>org.kde.optiimage</id>
  <name>OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">OptiImage</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxOptiImagexx</name>
  <provides>
    <binary>optiimage</binary>
  </provides>
  <summary>Image optimizer to reduce the size of images</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Optimitzador d'imatges per a reduir la mida de les imatges</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Optimitzador d'imatges per a reduir-ne la mida</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Irudien neurria murrizteko optimizatzaile bat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Optimalisatie van afbeeldingen om de grootte van afbeeldingen te verminderen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Görsellerin boyutunu azaltmak için bir görsel düzenleyicisi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Засіб оптимізації зображень, метою якого є зменшення розмірів файлів</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxImage optimizer to reduce the size of imagesxx</summary>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LGPL-2.1-only OR LGPL-3.0-only OR LicenseRef-KDE-Accepted-LGPL</project_license>
  <developer id="kde.org">
    <name>KDE</name>
  </developer>
  <description>
    <p>Optimize your images with OptiImage, a useful image compressor that supports
    PNG, JPEG, WebP and SVG file types.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Optimitzeu les imatges amb l'OptiImage, un compressor d'imatges útil que admet tipus de fitxers PNG, JPEG, WebP i SVG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Optimitzeu les imatges amb OptiImage, un compressor d'imatges útil que admet tipus de fitxers PNG, JPEG, WebP i SVG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Optimizatu zure irudiak OptiImage erabiliz, PNG, JPEG, WebP eta SVG fitxategi motak onartzen dituen irudi konprimatzaile baliagarri bat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Optimaliseer uw afbeeldingen met OptiImage, een nuttige comprimeerder die PNG, JPEG, WebP en SVG typen bestanden ondersteunt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">PNG, JPEG, WebP ve SVG türü görselleri destekleyen bir görsel sıkıştırıcısı olan OptiImage ile görsellerinizi eniyileyin.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Оптимізуйте ваші зображення за допомогою OptiImage, корисної програми для стискання файлів зображень, у якій передбачено підтримку типів файлів PNG, JPEG, WebP і SVG.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxOptimize your images with OptiImage, a useful image compressor that supports PNG, JPEG, WebP and SVG file types.xx</p>
    <p>It supports both lossless and lossy compression modes with an option to whether
    keep or not metadata of images. It additionally has a safe mode, where a new
    image is created instead of overwriting the old one.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">És compatible tant amb els modes de compressió amb pèrdua i sense, amb una opció per a mantenir o no les metadades de les imatges. A més, té un mode segur, on es crea una imatge nova en lloc de sobreescriure l'antiga.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">És compatible tant amb els modes de compressió amb pèrdua i sense, amb una opció per a mantindre o no les metadades de les imatges. A més, té un mode segur, on es crea una imatge nova en lloc de sobreescriure l'antiga.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Galerarik gabeko eta galeradun konpresio moduak, biak onartzen ditu, irudien meta-datuak mantendu edo ez erabakitzeko aukera batekin. Modu seguru bat ere badu, irudi zaharra gainidatzi ordez berri bat sortzeko.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Zowel compressiemodi met als zonder verlies worden ondersteund met een optie voor het al dan niet behouden van metagegevens van afbeeldingen. Bovendien met een veilige modus, waar een nieuwe afbeelding wordt gemaakt in plaats van de oude te overschrijven.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Görsellerin üst verisinin tutulup tutulmaması seçeneğiyle hem kayıpsız hem de kayıplı sıkıştırma kiplerini destekler. Ayrıca eskisinin üzerine yazmak yerine yeni bir görselin oluşturulduğu güvenli bir kipi da vardır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Передбачено підтримку режимів стискання без втрат та з втратами із можливістю зберігати або відкидати метадані зображень. Крім того, передбачено безпечний режим, у якому програма створює нове зображення замість перезапису старого.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxIt supports both lossless and lossy compression modes with an option to whether keep or not metadata of images. It additionally has a safe mode, where a new image is created instead of overwriting the old one.xx</p>
    <p>It uses the following tools:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Utilitza les eines següents:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Utilitza les eines següents:</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Ondoko tresnak erabiltzen ditu:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">De volgende hulpmiddelen worden gebruikt:</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Aşağıdaki araçları kullanır:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Використано такі інструменти:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxIt uses the following tools:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>oxipng for PNG images</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">«oxipng» per a imatges PNG</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">«oxipng» per a imatges PNG</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">oxipng PNG irudietarako</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">oxipng voor PNG-afbeeldingen</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">PNG görselleri için oxipng</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">oxipng для зображень PNG</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxoxipng for PNG imagesxx</li>
      <li>jpegoptim for JPEG images</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">«jpegoptim» per a imatges JPEG</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">«jpegoptim» per a imatges JPEG</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">jpegoptim JPEG irudietarako</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">jpegoptim voor JPEG-afbeeldingen</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">JPEG görselleri için jpegoptim</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">jpegoptim для зображень JPEG</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxjpegoptim for JPEG imagesxx</li>
      <li>scour for SVG images</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">«scour» per a imatges SVG</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">«scour» per a imatges SVG</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">scour SVG irudietarako</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">scour voor SVG-afbeeldingen</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">SVG görselleri için scour</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">scour для зображень SVG</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxscour for SVG imagesxx</li>
      <li>cwebp for WebP images</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">«cwebp» per a imatges WebP</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">«cwebp» per a imatges WebP</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">cwebp WebP irudietarako</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">cwebp voor WebP-afbeeldingen</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">WebP görselleri için cwebp</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">cwebp для зображень WebP</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxcwebp for WebP imagesxx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://invent.kde.org/carlschwan/optiimage</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=OptitImage</url>
  <categories>
    <category>Graphics</category>
  </categories>
  <custom>
    <value key="KDE::matrix">#plasma-mobile:kde.org</value>
  </custom>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.optiimage.desktop</launchable>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/optiimage/optiimage.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
</component>
